{
    "subject": "Princess_Jos\u00e9phine_Caroline_of_Belgium",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Prince_Karl_Anton_of_Hohenzollern",
    "human_readable": "Princess Jos\u00e9phine Caroline of Belgium is married to Prince Karl Anton of Hohenzollern.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9838082194328308,
            "question": "To whom is Princess Jos\u00e9phine Caroline of Belgium married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9837717413902283,
            "question": "Is Princess Jos\u00e9phine Caroline of Belgium married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9831180572509766,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Prince Karl Anton of Hohenzollern and Princess Jos\u00e9phine Caroline of Belgium?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9474031925201416,
            "question": "Who is married to Prince Karl Anton of Hohenzollern?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9469514489173889,
            "question": "What is the name of the Princess who is married to Prince Karl Anton of Hohenzollern?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7423018217086792,
            "question": "Which family does Prince Karl Anton of Hohenzollern belong to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3927306532859802,
            "question": "Can you identify a marriage between a princess and a prince?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.35945016145706177,
            "question": "What is the name of the princess involved in the marriage?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.0921938419342041,
            "question": "Is there a connection between two royal individuals mentioned?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.055267155170440674,
            "question": "Who are the royal figures mentioned in this statement?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Princess Jos\u00e9phine Caroline of Belgium is married to Prince Karl Anton of Hohenzollern.",
            "html": "yago_25909_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there a connection between two royal individuals mentioned?",
            "html": "yago_25909_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of the princess involved in the marriage?",
            "html": "yago_25909_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you identify a marriage between a princess and a prince?",
            "html": "yago_25909_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25909_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25909_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25909_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25909_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25909_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25909_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25909_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25909_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25909_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25909_75.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe query states that \"Princess Jos\u00e9phine Caroline of Belgium is married to Prince Karl Anton of Hohenzollern,\" which is supported by the information provided in the documents. Specifically, Document 63.txt confirms this relationship: \"On 28 May 1894 in Brussels, Karl Anton married his cousin Princess Jos\u00e9phine Caroline of Belgium (Brussels 18 October 1872-Namur 6 January 1958), daughter of Prince Philippe, Count of Flanders and his wife Princess Marie of Hohenzollern-Sigmaringen.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}